Loui happy man go with mr. Laszlo and
take care of his luggage certainly Rick
anything you say bye mr. Laszlo's
luggage and put it on the plane yes sir
this week you don't mind you fill in the
names I don't make it even more official
you think of everything then so and the
names are mr. and mrs. Victor Laszlo but
why my name Richard because you're
getting on that plane I don't understand
what about you I'm staying here with him
till the plane gets safely away nor it
shouldn't know what has happened to your
last night cousin actually said a great
many things you said I was to do the
thinking for both of us well I've done a
lot of it since then it all adds up to
one thing you're getting on that plane
with Victor where you belong to Richard
Lord now you've got to listen to me you
have any idea what you'd have to look
forward to if you stayed here nine
chances out of 10 we'd both wind up at a
concentration camp is not true Louie I'm
afraid major Strasser would insist
you're saying this honor to make me go
I'm saying it because it's true
inside of us we both know you belong
with Victor you're part of his work the
thing that keeps him going
if that plane leaves the ground and
you're not with him you'll regret it
maybe not today maybe not tomorrow but
soon and for the rest of your life but
what about us we'll always have Paris we
didn't have we we lost it until you came
to Casablanca got it back last night
and I said I would never leave you and
you never will
I've got a job to do to where I'm going
you can't follow what I've got to do you
can't be any part of those I'm not good
at being noble but it doesn't take much
to see that the problems of three little
people don't amount to a hill of beans
in this crazy world someday you
understand that
he's looking at you kid